<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on CIS 598 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on CIS 598 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/02-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/02-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>The major outcome for this course is a project that demonstrates your skills in computer science, software development, and other areas relevant to your chosen degree program. This page provides an overview that will help you get started on your project.
Recommended Timeline Here is a recommended timeline for your project:
Week 1: Identify a project, get a project advisor. Week 2: Report your project topic and advisor. Start developing. Week 3: &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; Complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation 1</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/03-presentation-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/03-presentation-1/</guid>
      <description>During the first half of the semester, each student will be scheduled to give a Overview &amp;amp; Requirements Presentation related to the project.
Presentation Outline The presentation should be roughly 8 minutes in length, and cover the following topics:
A brief overview of the project. A discussion of the requirements for each phase of the project. A proposed timeline for project completion. The first two items roughly correspond to the two initial artifacts discussed on the previous page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation 2</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/04-presentation-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/04-presentation-2/</guid>
      <description>During the second half of the semester, each student will be scheduled to give a Design Presentation related to the project.
Presentation Outline The presentation should be roughly 8 minutes in length, and cover the following topics:
The chosen design for the project. A deep overview of design diagrams relevant to the project: UML Diagrams (Class Diagrams, Sequence Diagrams, etc.) Database Entity Relationship Diagrams API Documentation Diagrams UI Mockups &amp;amp; Diagrams Sitemaps for Websites A discussion of how the project will be tested The first two items roughly correspond to the two initial artifacts discussed on the previous page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Presentation</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/05-final-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/05-final-presentation/</guid>
      <description>At the end of the semester, each student will give a public Final Presentation that presents all aspects of the completed project.
Overview The presentation should be roughly 30-45 minutes in length, and cover all aspects of the project. A recommended outline is below:
Introduction Background &amp;amp; Related Work Project Requirements Design Documents Project Implementation (Languages, Frameworks, Code Structure) Testing &amp;amp; Evaluation Packaging &amp;amp; Deployment (if applicable) Live Demo Future Work Conclusion Q&amp;amp;A Scheduling Final presentations are typically scheduled during the last week of the semester (sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;dead week&amp;rdquo;) or finals week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Artifacts</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/06-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/0-introduction/06-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>At the end of the semester, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to submit all of your project artifacts and information for grading. Here is a helpful checklist of everything that should be submitted:
Initial Writeup &amp;amp; Feature List (collected via Canvas early in the semester) First Presentation (collected via Canvas when it was presented) Second Presentation (collected via Canvas when it was presented) Advertisement Materials (collected via Canvas before final presentation) All Code &amp;amp; Related Resources Pushed to GitHub Classroom Repository Repository should include a README.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
