<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall 2022 :: CIS 598 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/index.html</link><description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598f22
Project Student Advisor Date Time Location K Finder Matthew Dubowski Thornton Wed., Dec. 7, 2022 12:30 - 1:15 DUE 2168 Shepherd’s Crossing Zane Roberts Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 8:15 - 9:00 DUE 2168 Terrestrial Things Graham Mathews Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 Case Master Charles “Trey” Bohlender Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 10:00 - 10:45 DUE 2183 Green.tld William Raymann Vasserman Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 11:30 - 12:15 DUE 2168 Project 1020 Web App Mason Lumley Feldhausen Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 12:15 -1:00 DUE 2168 Untitled Platformer Austen Clemons Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Spool API Caleb Niehues, Ashley Rediger, Christian Berard Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 2:45 - 5:00 DUE 2168 GPU Erasure Codes Ben Thompson Andresen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 8:15 - 9:00 DUE 2168 Quartz Markdown Editor Kirkland Akins Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 OrganizED College Dashboard Ahren Gann Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 9:45 - 10:30 DUE 2168 Foster Friend Katia Coleman Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 10:30 -11:15 DUE 2168 Gobang Game Zhuoer Ding Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 11:15 - 12:00 DUE 2168 Diabetic Management Program Steven Avila Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 1:00 - 1:45 DUE 2168 VCloset: A Virtual Closet Jay Brown Thornton Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 1:45 - 2:30 DUE 2168 ScaleUp Cameron Shilling Neilsen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 2:30 - 3:15 DUE 2168 The Book Brayden Pankaskie Shamir Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 3:15 - 4:00 DUE 2168 Slip NFC File Sending App Mason Potter Neilsen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 4:00 - 4:45 DUE 2168 MyEvents Laura Legg Feldhausen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 4:45 - 5:30 DUE 2168 Procedurally-Generated Atari Environments Mike Hulcy Hsu/Farrukh Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 Unknown Roguelike Haoran An Valenzuela Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 9:45 - 10:30 DUE 2168 Voxel Raytracer Ethan Tucker Hsu Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 10:30 -11:15 DUE 2168 Street Signs Analytics Rana Chevuru Hsu Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 11:15 - 12:00 DUE 2168 Wildcat Intramural Zane Myers, Adam Winter Feldhausen Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 1:00 - 2:30 DUE 2168 2D Multiplayer Game Paulina Olivas Feldhausen Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 2:30 - 3:15 DUE 2168 Fitness App Bhargav Marada Feldhausen Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 3:15 - 4:00 DUE 2168 Hyperbolic &amp; Multi Horizon Learning Algorithms Kevin Duong Hsu/Farrukh Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 4:00 - 4:45 DUE 2168 Aspiring 2D Platformer Charles Long Feldhausen Fri., Dec. 16, 2022 2:00 - 2:45 Zoom Link Context Textiles Amanda Dreesen Feldhausen Mon. Dec. 19, 2022 TBD Zoom Link Cow Reproduction App Joshua Garcia Bean Tue., Jan 17, 2023 9:20 - 10:30 DUE 2183 K Finder Matthew Dubowski</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>