<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall 2024 :: CIS 598 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/05-fall2024/index.html</link><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom GrooveMapper Sean Hackenberg Feldhausen Tue, Dec. 10 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom The Z-MAN Workout App Zachary Wilson Valenzuela Tue, Dec. 10 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom BlockOut: Employee Scheduling Simplified Alexander Valler DeLoach Tue, Dec. 10 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Quick Closet Ryan Stueve Bean Tue, Dec. 10 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Map Mates Matthew Cunningham Bean Tue, Dec. 10 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom DuelGames Mason Vick Feldhausen Tue, Dec. 10 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom K-12 CS Lesson Planning Wyatt Stella Bean Tue, Dec. 10 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Proximity-Aware Spell Correction Dennis Meyer Thornton Tue, Dec. 10 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Tabletop Role-Playing Game Character Sheet Creator Jackie Sadrakula Bean Tue, Dec. 10 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Cirrene Ethan Coleman Weese Tue, Dec. 10 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Productivity App Jadin O’Reillly Feldhausen Tue, Dec. 10 5:00 PM ONLINE Zoom Hidden Archive Sicheng Chen Bean Wed, Dec. 11 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Relevare Naomi Harrison Thornton Wed, Dec. 11 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Hacker’s Day Out Darius Tyson Bean Wed, Dec. 11 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Parrot Andrew Mejia Shamir Wed, Dec. 11 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Scoobot Jacob Prather Weese Wed, Dec. 11 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom GrapeVyne Lucas Boice Malallah Wed, Dec. 11 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Streamlink3D Garrett Jones Bean Wed, Dec. 11 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Smith House Managerial System Aidan Beesley Thornton Wed, Dec. 11 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom 4-H Fair Entry App Matthew Hall Feldhausen Wed, Dec. 11 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Wildcat Watershed Logan Smith Shamir Wed, Dec. 11 5:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom LibFlow Brian Carlos Feldhausen Fri, Dec. 13 9:30 AM ONLINE Zoom GrooveMapper Sean Hackenberg</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/05-fall2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>