<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Schedule :: CIS 598 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/index.html</link><description>Scheduled Presentation Times!</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall 2022</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/index.html</guid><description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598f22
Project Student Advisor Date Time Location K Finder Matthew Dubowski Thornton Wed., Dec. 7, 2022 12:30 - 1:15 DUE 2168 Shepherd’s Crossing Zane Roberts Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 8:15 - 9:00 DUE 2168 Terrestrial Things Graham Mathews Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 Case Master Charles “Trey” Bohlender Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 10:00 - 10:45 DUE 2183 Green.tld William Raymann Vasserman Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 11:30 - 12:15 DUE 2168 Project 1020 Web App Mason Lumley Feldhausen Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 12:15 -1:00 DUE 2168 Untitled Platformer Austen Clemons Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Spool API Caleb Niehues, Ashley Rediger, Christian Berard Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 2:45 - 5:00 DUE 2168 GPU Erasure Codes Ben Thompson Andresen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 8:15 - 9:00 DUE 2168 Quartz Markdown Editor Kirkland Akins Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 OrganizED College Dashboard Ahren Gann Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 9:45 - 10:30 DUE 2168 Foster Friend Katia Coleman Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 10:30 -11:15 DUE 2168 Gobang Game Zhuoer Ding Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 11:15 - 12:00 DUE 2168 Diabetic Management Program Steven Avila Weese Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 1:00 - 1:45 DUE 2168 VCloset: A Virtual Closet Jay Brown Thornton Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 1:45 - 2:30 DUE 2168 ScaleUp Cameron Shilling Neilsen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 2:30 - 3:15 DUE 2168 The Book Brayden Pankaskie Shamir Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 3:15 - 4:00 DUE 2168 Slip NFC File Sending App Mason Potter Neilsen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 4:00 - 4:45 DUE 2168 MyEvents Laura Legg Feldhausen Wed., Dec. 14, 2022 4:45 - 5:30 DUE 2168 Procedurally-Generated Atari Environments Mike Hulcy Hsu/Farrukh Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 Unknown Roguelike Haoran An Valenzuela Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 9:45 - 10:30 DUE 2168 Voxel Raytracer Ethan Tucker Hsu Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 10:30 -11:15 DUE 2168 Street Signs Analytics Rana Chevuru Hsu Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 11:15 - 12:00 DUE 2168 Wildcat Intramural Zane Myers, Adam Winter Feldhausen Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 1:00 - 2:30 DUE 2168 2D Multiplayer Game Paulina Olivas Feldhausen Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 2:30 - 3:15 DUE 2168 Fitness App Bhargav Marada Feldhausen Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 3:15 - 4:00 DUE 2168 Hyperbolic &amp; Multi Horizon Learning Algorithms Kevin Duong Hsu/Farrukh Thu., Dec. 15, 2022 4:00 - 4:45 DUE 2168 Aspiring 2D Platformer Charles Long Feldhausen Fri., Dec. 16, 2022 2:00 - 2:45 Zoom Link Context Textiles Amanda Dreesen Feldhausen Mon. Dec. 19, 2022 TBD Zoom Link Cow Reproduction App Joshua Garcia Bean Tue., Jan 17, 2023 9:20 - 10:30 DUE 2183 K Finder Matthew Dubowski</description></item><item><title>Spring 2023</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/02-spring2023/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/02-spring2023/index.html</guid><description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598s23
Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Where to Look - Cyber Sensor Placement and Calibration Chase Barber
Kale DeYoung
Kaleb Ernst
Nathan Fleming
Nathan Wells Vasserman Mon., May 1, 2023 1:00 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Hydroponics Management System Cashel FitzGibbons Neilsen Tues., May 9, 2023 8:00 - 8:45 DUE 2168 Day to Remember Eve Steinle Bean Tues., May 9, 2023 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 SharePoint Resource Management Tool John Velasco Feldhausen Tues., May 9, 2023 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 ClarifAI Patrick Moll Thornton Tues., May 9, 2023 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 SongSwap Jared Bothwell Feldhausen Tues., May 9, 2023 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 EasyCart Connor Wiggins Thornton Tues., May 9, 2023 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Improviso Cody Murphy Weese Tues., May 9, 2023 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 3D Printing Monitor Framework Quentin Ricketts Neilsen Tues., May 9, 2023 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Team Based Pixel Game Sean Hurt Feldhausen Tues., May 9, 2023 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 Magical Casters Jordan Miller Hsu Tues., May 9, 2023 5:00 - 5:45 DUE 2168 Web of Smithies Eric Yu Shamir Wed., May 10, 2023 8:00 - 8:45 DUE 2168 Predictive Golf Tournament Model Mason Wittman Shamir Wed., May 10, 2023 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 Worlds Without Number Faction Simulator Evelyn Gruver Hsu Wed., May 10, 2023 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Interactions Between Nations Through Trade Rana Chevuru Shamir Wed., May 10, 2023 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 NexdMovie Parker Billinger Hsu Wed., May 10, 2023 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 Quictionary Marco Vasquez Valenzuela Wed., May 10, 2023 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Realistic Biome Generator Sam McAnany Valenzuela Wed., May 10, 2023 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 ViShader Eric Honas Bean Wed., May 10, 2023 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Dou Dizhu Ziyu Zhao Bean Wed., May 10, 2023 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 FrontPage Ethan Hulen Bean Wed., May 10, 2023 3:30 - 4:15 DUE 2168 Geoplay Kaden O’Hare Weese Wed., May 10, 2023 4:15 - 5:00 DUE 2168 Climate-Control and Data Logging System for Mycelium Growing Isaac Peterson Neilsen Wed., May 10, 2023 5:00 - 5:45 DUE 2168 Dungeon Swing Micah Roening Weese Thur., May 11, 2023 8:00 - 8:45 DUE 2168 What’s Next Connor Gabrielson McGinty Thur., May 11, 2023 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 Legion DB Nicholas Friesen Caragea Thur., May 11, 2023 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Analyses of Institutional Reputation through Social Media Data Mining Adam Clement Caragea Thur., May 11, 2023 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 Personal Financial Planning Assistant Garrett Heitmann Thornton Thur., May 11, 2023 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 ELA Platform Colton Capps Feldhausen Thur., May 11, 2023 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Spells and Shapes Kirkland Akins Bean Thur., May 11, 2023 1:00 - 1:45 DUE 2168 Speakeasy Parker Schmitt Feldhausen Thur., May 11, 2023 1:45 - 2:30 DUE 2168 AD Discord Bot Reece Miller Feldhausen Thur., May 11, 2023 2:30 - 3:15 DUE 2168 The Resurrection of A Project of Voice Alisha Crow Weese Thur., May 11, 2023 3:15 - 4:00 DUE 2168 Pass Keeper Tucker Deaton Feldhausen Fri., May 12, 2023 12:00 - 12:45 DUE 2168 Where to Look - Cyber Sensor Placement and Calibration Chase Barber
Kale DeYoung
Kaleb Ernst
Nathan Fleming
Nathan Wells</description></item><item><title>Fall 2023</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/03-fall2023/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/03-fall2023/index.html</guid><description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598s23
Project Student Advisor Date Time Location SDN API Security Alexander Ozga, Ryan Rosenkoetter, Zachary Zollers Amariucai Tue, Dec 12 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 Valkyrie Taylor Howell Bean Tue, Dec 12 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Simple Calendar Hursen Adjovi Weese Tue, Dec 12 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 Ambassador Toolkit Andrew Varguez Weese Tue, Dec 12 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 Slang Embedded Systems Interfacing Jacob Legg Hatcliff Tue, Dec 12 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Boiler Control Verification Gage Hawbaker Hatcliff Tue, Dec 12 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Flood Watch Mitchell Hutchinson Weese Tue, Dec 12 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Pocket Pike John Schaefer Valenzuela Tue, Dec 12 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 Yik Yak Clone Isaiah McAdam Thornton Tue, Dec 12 3:30 - 4:15 DUE 2168 SkyDive Atlas Jack Rigdon Feldhausen Tue, Dec 12 4:15 - 5:00 DUE 2168 FitPlan-AI Ethan Khoury Bean Wed, Dec 13 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Equivalent Learning Activity Platform Ben Sherwood Bean Wed, Dec 13 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 Black Student Union Website Manny Adeniji Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 Greek Central Lili Chen Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Knowledge Graph Generator Caleb Martin McGinty Wed, Dec 13 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Recipe Radar Cade Robinson Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Room Tally Darius McAdam Neilsen Wed, Dec 13 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 Red Cedar Forage Loss Calculator Britain Modean Neilsen Wed, Dec 13 3:30 - 4:15 DUE 2168 Insight Social Gunnar Harmon Caragea Wed, Dec 13 4:15 - 5:00 DUE 2168 WeReader Caeden Venters Andresen Fri, Dec 15 10:00 - 11:00 DUE 2183 SDN API Security Alexander Ozga, Ryan Rosenkoetter, Zachary Zollers</description></item><item><title>Spring 2024</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/04-spring2024/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/04-spring2024/index.html</guid><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom Cook Chuhao Chen Feldhausen Thu, May 2 12:00 DUE 2168 Zoom HAL Abdullah Rasheed Amtoft Thu, May 2 2:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Momentum Productivity Luke Horsch Bean Thu, May 2 3:30 DUE 2168 Zoom Task Management Dashboard Sam Boese Thornton Fri, May 3 10:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Ecifircas Jonah Bogusch Thornton Fri, May 3 11:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Beat Canvas Hunter Pfannenstiel &amp; Payton Pfannenstiel DeLoach Fri, May 3 11:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Librus Nathan Lee Weese Fri, May 3 1:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Scratch Auto Grader Joshua Barron Bean Fri, May 3 2:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Toy Tank Royale Jarrod Moore Bean Fri, May 3 2:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Managerial Assistance Contact Console Max Maus Feldhausen Fri, May 3 4:15 DUE 2168 Zoom MyFlossBox Megan Blankenship Feldhausen Mon, May 6 8:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Minimum Wage Matters Carrie Aponte Shamir &amp; Malallah Mon, May 6 9:30 DUE 2168 Zoom St. Isidore’s Library Management System Gabriel Whitehair Thornton Mon, May 6 10:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Kansas State GPS Map Andrew Barrett Vasserman Mon, May 6 11:00 DUE 2168 Zoom The Cookbook Sebastian Trill Lang Mon, May 6 1:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Prowess Picks Alex Heinking Shamir Mon, May 6 2:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Procedural Surface Destruction System Bryan Su Amtoft Mon, May 6 2:45 DUE 2168 Zoom RPG Squared Garrett Love Bean Mon, May 6 3:30 DUE 2168 Zoom Sentiment Analysis Chatbot Aubriana Gonzalez Caragea Mon, May 6 4:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Saudi Students Club Jyad Aljohani Caragea Tue, May 7 9:30 DUE 2168 Zoom CheckMate Chibuike Samuel Eze Shamir Tue, May 7 9:30 DUE 2183 Zoom Grocery Master Brian Vu Caragea Tue, May 7 10:15 DUE 2183 Zoom Ethereum Wireshark Dissector Jacob Bengel, Garrett Brown, Justin Sanders, Colin O’Donnell &amp; Lex Weeks Vasserman Tue, May 7 11:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Kansas State Crew Utils Mason Phillips Feldhausen Tue, May 7 11:45 DUE 2183 Zoom Instant Workout Izabel Romero &amp; Joe DeWitt Thornton Tue, May 7 1:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Sanctum TTRPG Character Sheet Web App Johnathan Partridge Weese Tue, May 7 1:15 DUE 2183 Zoom 3Depot Kyle Reading Bean Tue, May 7 2:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Echo Insight Jacob Howard DeLoach Tue, May 7 2:45 DUE 2183 Zoom K-State Free Yoga Emma Lucas Feldhausen Tue, May 7 3:30 DUE 2168 Zoom Cool Map Generation Nicholas Sixbury Bean Tue, May 7 3:30 DUE 2183 Zoom Wildcat Connect Mason Noll Shamir Tue, May 7 4:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Evolution Simulator Jonnathan Taylor DeLoach Tue, May 7 4:15 DUE 2183 Zoom Spotify Custom Shuffle Feature David Bures Shamir Wed, May 8 8:45 DUE 2168 Zoom ACM Member Portal Samuel Haynes Feldhausen Wed, May 8 8:45 DUE 2183 Zoom Typlee Heidi Cossins Valenzuela Wed, May 8 9:30 DUE 2168 Zoom Nine Men’s Morris AlphaZero AI Brent Howe Hsu Wed, May 8 9:30 DUE 2183 Zoom Gym Friends Jadin O’Reilly Bean Wed, May 8 10:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Gamecraft Collin Hammond Valenzuela Wed, May 8 10:15 DUE 2183 Zoom Links Leader Blake Spencer Valenzuela Wed, May 8 11:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Survival Island Alexander Bingham Lang Wed, May 8 11:00 DUE 2183 Zoom SportSync Ryan Schmideskamp Valenzuela Wed, May 8 11:45 DUE 2168 Zoom BookMate Chris Brown Feldhausen Wed, May 8 11:45 DUE 2183 Zoom Milkcrate Nick Leskovac Weese Wed, May 8 1:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Content Creator Bot Jordan Bui Valenzuela Wed, May 8 1:15 DUE 2183 Zoom Wheels’Waves Will Hackemer Valenzuela Wed, May 8 2:00 DUE 2168 Zoom ResumeAuto Biruk Cherie Neilsen Wed, May 8 2:00 DUE 2183 Zoom Herd Alert Jake Stetson Caragea Wed, May 8 2:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Choon Spencer Montag Valenzuela Wed, May 8 2:45 DUE 2183 Zoom Threadfolio Meghan Buchanan Malallah Wed, May 8 3:30 DUE 2168 Zoom Progressive Overload Gus Obour Bean Wed, May 8 3:30 DUE 2183 Zoom SmallBiz MS Jackson Huffman &amp; Logan Newsom Weese Wed, May 8 4:15 DUE 2183 Zoom Cook Chuhao Chen</description></item><item><title>Fall 2024</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/05-fall2024/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/05-fall2024/index.html</guid><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom GrooveMapper Sean Hackenberg Feldhausen Tue, Dec. 10 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom The Z-MAN Workout App Zachary Wilson Valenzuela Tue, Dec. 10 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom BlockOut: Employee Scheduling Simplified Alexander Valler DeLoach Tue, Dec. 10 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Quick Closet Ryan Stueve Bean Tue, Dec. 10 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Map Mates Matthew Cunningham Bean Tue, Dec. 10 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom DuelGames Mason Vick Feldhausen Tue, Dec. 10 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom K-12 CS Lesson Planning Wyatt Stella Bean Tue, Dec. 10 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Proximity-Aware Spell Correction Dennis Meyer Thornton Tue, Dec. 10 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Tabletop Role-Playing Game Character Sheet Creator Jackie Sadrakula Bean Tue, Dec. 10 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Cirrene Ethan Coleman Weese Tue, Dec. 10 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Productivity App Jadin O’Reillly Feldhausen Tue, Dec. 10 5:00 PM ONLINE Zoom Hidden Archive Sicheng Chen Bean Wed, Dec. 11 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Relevare Naomi Harrison Thornton Wed, Dec. 11 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Hacker’s Day Out Darius Tyson Bean Wed, Dec. 11 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Parrot Andrew Mejia Shamir Wed, Dec. 11 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Scoobot Jacob Prather Weese Wed, Dec. 11 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom GrapeVyne Lucas Boice Malallah Wed, Dec. 11 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Streamlink3D Garrett Jones Bean Wed, Dec. 11 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Smith House Managerial System Aidan Beesley Thornton Wed, Dec. 11 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom 4-H Fair Entry App Matthew Hall Feldhausen Wed, Dec. 11 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Wildcat Watershed Logan Smith Shamir Wed, Dec. 11 5:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom LibFlow Brian Carlos Feldhausen Fri, Dec. 13 9:30 AM ONLINE Zoom GrooveMapper Sean Hackenberg</description></item><item><title>Spring 2025</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/06-spring2025/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/06-spring2025/index.html</guid><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom GarageMate Sam Wilson Weese Tue, May 13 8:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom After Hours Kyle Zeller Feldhausen Tue, May 13 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Eat-Seats Dawson Stutzman Bean Tue, May 13 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Another Voxel Engine Cameron Pilchard Feldhausen Tue, May 13 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom PeakTri Sage Cauley Feldhausen Tue, May 13 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Superorganism Jiwoo Jung DeLoach Tue, May 13 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Only In My Head Keenan Melton Bean Tue, May 13 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom RollScape Samuel Allred Bean Tue, May 13 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom MTG DND Card Cost Calculator Camden Green Bean Tue, May 13 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom SightSeer Interactive Mapping Gabriel McReynolds Valenzuela Tue, May 13 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom SwiftMail Caleb Chan Thornton Tue, May 13 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom McToStl Wyatt Smith DeLoach Wed, May 14 8:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Pokedex Tushar Lanka Neilsen Wed, May 14 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom SimTrade Vinny Sun Weese Wed, May 14 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Screen Savior Caleb Kmiecik Shamir Wed, May 14 9:30 AM DUE 2183 Zoom Potion Match Maxwell Shafer Bean Wed, May 14 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Escaplore Sak Lee Neilsen Wed, May 14 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Puzzle Mate Kyle Kohman Thornton Wed, May 14 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom RecallFlow Lukas Hurtig Feldhausen Wed, May 14 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom DataDunk Isaac Steiner Valenzuela Wed, May 14 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Fredbear and Friends: Arcade Bryan Gross Bean Wed, May 14 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom MicroMouse Maze Solving John Woods Hsu Wed, May 14 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom The Fridge Alex Harper Feldhausen Wed, May 14 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Pickelball Planner Dylan Rosquist Valenzuela Thur, May 15 8:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Desmos Clone Kael Pavlik DeLoach Thur, May 15 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom DiscMate Moises Villegas Valenzuela Thur, May 15 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Local Concert Tatenda Sekabanja Malallah Thur, May 15 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom WorkAlert Clint McKenzie &amp; Logan Arnold Feldhausen Thur, May 15 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Webcipe Pedro Mendez-Alcantar Feldhausen Thur, May 15 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Macro Motive Matthew Lund Feldhausen Thur, May 15 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Hearth Aaron McKain Thornton Thur, May 15 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Penguin Physics Thomas Rosebrook Bean Thur, May 15 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom GarageMate Sam Wilson</description></item><item><title>Fall 2025</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/07-fall2025/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/07-fall2025/index.html</guid><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom ServiceSync Nate Carter Thornton Fri, Dec 12 1:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom How Random is Pseudorandom? Ryan Welch &amp; Dillon McGinn Amariucai Tue, Dec 16 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Verba Wyatt Morris Weese Wed, Dec 17 8:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom CourseLogiCS Jackson Cannell Malallah Wed, Dec 17 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom EduVista Taj Ikhlaas Malallah Wed, Dec 17 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Bizzi Ayden Wyer Bean Wed, Dec 17 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Pharma In Review Daniel Robertson McGinty Wed, Dec 17 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Draw Fight Kit Hawkins Andresen Wed, Dec 17 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom BeefBase Carson Toews Weese Wed, Dec 17 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom BoardClaimed Matthew Gwaltney Bean Wed, Dec 17 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom TrailBlazer Jack Schaeffer James Wed, Dec 17 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Molecule Generation with Graph Neural Networks Greyson Walker McGinty Wed, Dec 17 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom SmartDisc Daniel Chang Valenzuela Wed, Dec 17 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Project Manager Charlie Bergdall Feldhausen Thur, Dec 18 9:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Iron Rank Cayden Hoffman Bean Thur, Dec 18 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Hide and Seek Cars Madeleine Smith Andresen Thur, Dec 18 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Fragrance Genie Chipo Sekabanja Shamir Thur, Dec 18 12:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Kansas Population Trends Visualization Amala John, Evan Harris, &amp; Josh Zrubek Bean Thur, Dec 18 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom DashTA Hiep Nguyen Malallah Thur, Dec 18 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Gig Manager Carson Bollinger Thornton Thur, Dec 18 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Aerosuite Ella Carlson Feldhausen Fri, Dec 19 10:30 AM Virtual Zoom Agricultural Microworld Max Casey, Daniel Cortez, Dakota Denton, &amp; Jackson Saim Bean Fri, Dec 19 11:50 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Threadfolio Meghan Buchanan Feldhausen Fri, Dec 19 4:00 PM Virtual Zoom BirthOrder Cole Hayden Andresen Tue, Dec 23 3:30 PM Virtual Zoom 3D Shop Josef Aranjo Feldhausen Wed, Jan 7 10:00 AM Virtual Zoom ServiceSync Nate Carter</description></item></channel></rss>