<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Schedule :: CIS 598 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/</link><description>Scheduled Presentation Times!</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall 2022</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/</guid><description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598f22
Project Student Advisor Date Time Location K Finder Matthew Dubowski Thornton Wed., Dec. 7, 2022 12:30 - 1:15 DUE 2168 Shepherd’s Crossing Zane Roberts Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 8:15 - 9:00 DUE 2168 Terrestrial Things Graham Mathews Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 Case Master Charles “Trey” Bohlender Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 10:00 - 10:45 DUE 2183 Green.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2023</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/02-spring2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/02-spring2023/</guid><description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598s23
Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Where to Look - Cyber Sensor Placement and Calibration Chase Barber
Kale DeYoung
Kaleb Ernst
Nathan Fleming
Nathan Wells Vasserman Mon., May 1, 2023 1:00 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Hydroponics Management System Cashel FitzGibbons Neilsen Tues., May 9, 2023 8:00 - 8:45 DUE 2168 Day to Remember Eve Steinle Bean Tues., May 9, 2023 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 SharePoint Resource Management Tool John Velasco Feldhausen Tues.</description></item><item><title>Fall 2023</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/03-fall2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/03-fall2023/</guid><description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598s23
Project Student Advisor Date Time Location SDN API Security Alexander Ozga, Ryan Rosenkoetter, Zachary Zollers Amariucai Tue, Dec 12 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 Valkyrie Taylor Howell Bean Tue, Dec 12 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Simple Calendar Hursen Adjovi Weese Tue, Dec 12 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 Ambassador Toolkit Andrew Varguez Weese Tue, Dec 12 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 Slang Embedded Systems Interfacing Jacob Legg Hatcliff Tue, Dec 12 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Boiler Control Verification Gage Hawbaker Hatcliff Tue, Dec 12 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Flood Watch Mitchell Hutchinson Weese Tue, Dec 12 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Pocket Pike John Schaefer Valenzuela Tue, Dec 12 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 Yik Yak Clone Isaiah McAdam Thornton Tue, Dec 12 3:30 - 4:15 DUE 2168 SkyDive Atlas Jack Rigdon Feldhausen Tue, Dec 12 4:15 - 5:00 DUE 2168 FitPlan-AI Ethan Khoury Bean Wed, Dec 13 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Equivalent Learning Activity Platform Ben Sherwood Bean Wed, Dec 13 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 Black Student Union Website Manny Adeniji Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 Greek Central Lili Chen Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Knowledge Graph Generator Caleb Martin McGinty Wed, Dec 13 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Recipe Radar Cade Robinson Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Room Tally Darius McAdam Neilsen Wed, Dec 13 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 Red Cedar Forage Loss Calculator Britain Modean Neilsen Wed, Dec 13 3:30 - 4:15 DUE 2168 Insight Social Gunnar Harmon Caragea Wed, Dec 13 4:15 - 5:00 DUE 2168 WeReader Caeden Venters Andresen Fri, Dec 15 10:00 - 11:00 DUE 2183 SDN API Security Alexander Ozga, Ryan Rosenkoetter, Zachary Zollers</description></item><item><title>Spring 2024</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/04-spring2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/04-spring2024/</guid><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom Cook Chuhao Chen Feldhausen Thu, May 2 12:00 DUE 2168 Zoom HAL Abdullah Rasheed Amtoft Thu, May 2 2:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Momentum Productivity Luke Horsch Bean Thu, May 2 3:30 DUE 2168 Zoom Task Management Dashboard Sam Boese Thornton Fri, May 3 10:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Ecifircas Jonah Bogusch Thornton Fri, May 3 11:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Beat Canvas Hunter Pfannenstiel &amp; Payton Pfannenstiel DeLoach Fri, May 3 11:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Librus Nathan Lee Weese Fri, May 3 1:15 DUE 2168 Zoom Scratch Auto Grader Joshua Barron Bean Fri, May 3 2:00 DUE 2168 Zoom Toy Tank Royale Jarrod Moore Bean Fri, May 3 2:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Managerial Assistance Contact Console Max Maus Feldhausen Fri, May 3 4:15 DUE 2168 Zoom MyFlossBox Megan Blankenship Feldhausen Mon, May 6 8:45 DUE 2168 Zoom Minimum Wage Matters Carrie Aponte Shamir &amp; Malallah Mon, May 6 9:30 DUE 2168 Zoom St.</description></item><item><title>Fall 2024</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/05-fall2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/05-fall2024/</guid><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom GrooveMapper Sean Hackenberg Feldhausen Tue, Dec. 10 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom The Z-MAN Workout App Zachary Wilson Valenzuela Tue, Dec. 10 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom BlockOut: Employee Scheduling Simplified Alexander Valler DeLoach Tue, Dec. 10 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Quick Closet Ryan Stueve Bean Tue, Dec. 10 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Map Mates Matthew Cunningham Bean Tue, Dec. 10 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom DuelGames Mason Vick Feldhausen Tue, Dec.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2025</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/06-spring2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/b-schedule/06-spring2025/</guid><description>Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Zoom Title Sam Wilson Weese Tue, May 13 8:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Kyle Zeller Feldhausen Tue, May 13 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Dawson Stutzman Bean Tue, May 13 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Cameron Pilchard Feldhausen Tue, May 13 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Sage Cauley Feldhausen Tue, May 13 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Jiwoo Jung DeLoach Tue, May 13 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Keenan Melton Bean Tue, May 13 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Samuel Allred Bean Tue, May 13 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Camden Green Bean Tue, May 13 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Gabriel McReynolds Valenzuela Tue, May 13 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Caleb Chan Thornton Tue, May 13 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Wyatt Smith DeLoach Wed, May 14 8:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Tushar Lanka Neilsen Wed, May 14 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Vinny Sun Weese Wed, May 14 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Maxwell Shafer Bean Wed, May 14 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Sak Lee Neilsen Wed, May 14 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Kyle Kohman Thornton Wed, May 14 11:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Lukas Hurtig Feldhausen Wed, May 14 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Isaac Steiner Valenzuela Wed, May 14 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Bryan Gross Bean Wed, May 14 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title John Woods Hsu Wed, May 14 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Alex Harper Feldhausen Wed, May 14 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Dylan Rosquist Valenzuela Thur, May 15 8:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Kael Pavlik DeLoach Thur, May 15 8:45 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Moises Villegas Valenzuela Thur, May 15 9:30 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Tatenda Sekabanja Malallah Thur, May 15 10:15 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Clint McKenzie &amp; Logan Arnold Feldhausen Thur, May 15 11:00 AM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Pedro Mendez-Alcantar Feldhausen Thur, May 15 1:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Matthew Lund Feldhausen Thur, May 15 2:00 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Aaron McKain Thornton Thur, May 15 2:45 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Thomas Rosebrook Bean Thur, May 15 3:30 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Title Student Name Advisor Thur, May 15 4:15 PM DUE 2168 Zoom Project Name Sam Wilson</description></item></channel></rss>