




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Schedule on CIS 598 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Schedule on CIS 598 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2022</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/01-fall2022/index.html</guid>
      <description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598f22 Project Student Advisor Date Time Location K Finder Matthew Dubowski Thornton Wed., Dec. 7, 2022 12:30 - 1:15 DUE 2168 Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s Crossing Zane Roberts Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 8:15 - 9:00 DUE 2168 Terrestrial Things Graham Mathews Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 9:00 - 9:45 DUE 2168 Case Master Charles &amp;ldquo;Trey&amp;rdquo; Bohlender Bean Tue., Dec. 13, 2022 10:00 - 10:45 DUE 2183 Green.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring 2023</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/02-spring2023/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/02-spring2023/index.html</guid>
      <description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598s23 Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Where to Look - Cyber Sensor Placement and Calibration Chase Barber
Kale DeYoung
Kaleb Ernst
Nathan Fleming
Nathan Wells Vasserman Mon., May 1, 2023 1:00 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Hydroponics Management System Cashel FitzGibbons Neilsen Tues., May 9, 2023 8:00 - 8:45 DUE 2168 Day to Remember Eve Steinle Bean Tues., May 9, 2023 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 SharePoint Resource Management Tool John Velasco Feldhausen Tues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2023</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/03-fall2023/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis598/b-schedule/03-fall2023/index.html</guid>
      <description>All presentations will be streamed on Zoom at https://bit.ly/cis598s23 Project Student Advisor Date Time Location Project Title Alexander Ozga, Ryan Rosenkoetter, Zachary Zollers Amariucai Tue, Dec 12 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 Project Title Student Name Advisor Tue, Dec 12 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Project Title Hursen Adjovi Weese Tue, Dec 12 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 Project Title Andrew Varguez Weese Tue, Dec 12 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 Project Title Jacob Legg Hatcliff Tue, Dec 12 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Project Title Gage Hawbaker Hatcliff Tue, Dec 12 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Project Title Mitchell Hutchinson Weese Tue, Dec 12 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Project Title John Schaefer Valenzuela Tue, Dec 12 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 Project Title Isaiah McAdam Thornton Tue, Dec 12 3:30 - 4:15 DUE 2168 Project Title Jack Rigdon Feldhausen Tue, Dec 12 4:15 - 5:00 DUE 2168 Project Title Student Name Advisor Wed, Dec 13 8:45 - 9:30 DUE 2168 Project Title Student Name Advisor Wed, Dec 13 9:30 - 10:15 DUE 2168 Project Title Ben Sherwood Bean Wed, Dec 13 10:15 - 11:00 DUE 2168 Project Title Manny Adeniji Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 11:00 - 11:45 DUE 2168 Project Title Lili Chen Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 11:45 - 12:30 DUE 2168 Project Title Caleb Martin McGinty Wed, Dec 13 1:15 - 2:00 DUE 2168 Project Title Cade Robinson Feldhausen Wed, Dec 13 2:00 - 2:45 DUE 2168 Project Title Darius McAdam Neilsen Wed, Dec 13 2:45 - 3:30 DUE 2168 Project Title Britain Modean Neilsen Wed, Dec 13 3:30 - 4:15 DUE 2168 Project Title Student Name Advisor Wed, Dec 13 4:15 - 5:00 DUE 2168 Project Title Alexander Ozga, Ryan Rosenkoetter, Zachary Zollers</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>