<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall 2024 Syllabus :: CIS 598 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/0-introduction/01-syllabus/old/fall2024/index.html</link><description>CIS 596 - Entrepreneurial Computer Science Project - Fall 2024 CIS 598 - Computer Science Project - Fall 2024 Instructor Contact Information Instructor: Dr. Scott DeLoach (sdeloach AT ksu DOT edu) Office: DUE 2184 Phone: (785) 532-6350 Website: https://people.cs.ksu.edu/~sdeloach/ Office Hours: TBA
Instructor: Russell Feldhausen (russfeld AT ksu DOT edu)
I use he/him pronouns. Feel free to share your own pronouns with me, and I’ll do my best to use them! Office: DUE 2213, but I mostly work remotely from Kansas City, MO Phone: (785) 292-3121 (Call/Text) Website: https://russfeld.me Virtual Office Hours: By appointment via Zoom. Schedule a meeting at https://calendly.com/russfeld Preferred Methods of Communication: Email: Students should email questions directly to the instructors. We will try to respond within one business day. Chat: You may find instructors online via the CS department Discord server and Microsoft Teams. We will try to respond when we can, but if you don’t get a response please email us. Phone/Text: Emergencies only! We will do our best to respond as quickly as we can. Prerequisites CIS 596: CIS 560, ENTRP 340 and senior standing in computer science. Students may enroll in CIS courses only if they have earned a grade of C or better for each prerequisite to those courses. CIS 598: CIS 560 and senior standing in computer science. Students may enroll in CIS courses only if they have earned a grade of C or better for each prerequisite to those courses. Course Overview Directed studies: selection, investigation and report on some topic not covered in prior courses; may include an implementation and/or experimentation component; may be done in collaboration with other students. Completion of a final report with literature review and project evaluation.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/0-introduction/01-syllabus/old/fall2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>