<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resources :: CIS 598 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/index.html</link><description>Helpful Resources!</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Links</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/01-links/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/01-links/index.html</guid><description>This page is a collection of general links that may be useful. Email the instructors to request any additions.
System Design Textbook - a great writeup on system design, starting from the basics of networking and the internet through high availability systems and case studies. This information is very useful as you get closer to having a product ready for release and deployment, but may also help inform your early design stage as well.</description></item><item><title>CIS 748 Videos</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/02-cis748-videos/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/02-cis748-videos/index.html</guid><description>This page contains links to videos and some comments from the CIS 748: Advanced Software Management course taught by Dr. DeLoach.
YouTube Channel - contains all videos.
Video Topics Below is a quick guide to the various videos and their relevance to CIS 598 projects. Feel free to use this to help you find a particular video or topic.
Chapter 1: Videos 1a and 1b talk mostly about project teams. 1a also covers work products. 1c talks about different approaches to a project, and may be helpful during initial project planning stages. Chapter 2: Video 2b gives some useful information about software development processes. 2c is some good historical information as well. Videos 2d and 2e are super useful since they cover both iterative and agile development, which is the most common development process employed by students in this course. Chapter 3: The videos from chapter 3 are useful during the early parts of the project and give lots of information about how to determine the features and requirements for a project. Watching these videos early on may help you ideate around your project. Chapter 4: Chapter 4 is mostly related to large software projects and may not be directly relevant, but is still useful in some areas. Chapter 5: Chapter 5 covers large project management, which may be a bit outside the scope of CIS 598 but is interesting if you plan on joining or managing a large software team in the future. Chapter 6: The content in chapter 6 goes deep into project estimation, and is probably too deep for CIS 598. However, some of the content may help give you a few ideas for how to judge the approximate scope and scale of your project as you get further into planning. Chapter 7: I recommend watching some of the content in Chapter 7 on time management and evaluating progress about halfway through the semester. They can be a good prompt for reflection as you reach the halfway point and look ahead to the last part of the project. Chapter 8: Chapter 8 is mostly on value analysis, which is not really relevant to CIS 598. Chapter 9: Likewise, Chapter 9 mostly covers risk management, which is probably not relevant to most CIS 598 projects.</description></item><item><title>Presentation Tips</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/03-presentation-tips/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/03-presentation-tips/index.html</guid><description>This is a presentation tips video recorded during the Fall 2022 semester.
Edited Transcript Hello, everyone, I wanted to take a few minutes to record a short video to give you some tips and tricks of things that you can do to improve your presentations for the second round of presentations. Most of these comments are from things that Dr. DeLoach, Dr. Lang and I wrote down on the comment sheets for all of you, those should all be uploaded to Canvas. And if you don’t see that, let me know. And I can find your comment sheet and make sure it gets attached to the comments on canvas. But what I’m going to do is I’m going to go through a few slides examples and talk about a few things that we really noticed in these presentations that are things that you can work on to improve for the next time around.</description></item><item><title>Projects &amp; Time Tracking</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/04-projects-time/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis598/a-resources/04-projects-time/index.html</guid><description>This is a video exploring GitHub Projects &amp; Clockify Time Tracking for Spring 2023
Edited Transcript Hello, in this video, I’m going to talk through a bit of the process of doing time tracking in CIS 598, as well as doing some project management using GitHub, through the GitHub projects interface. First and foremost, what I’ve pulled up is Clockify, I’ve invited everybody in the class to Clockify this semester for our time tracking. Clockify is a free application that you can use to keep track of what you’re working on. And I think it has some really useful features that will make this class go a lot faster. So when you first log in to Clockify you’ll be able to select both the timesheet and the time tracker. The timesheet is pretty simple. It’s a traditional timesheet where you list all your projects, and then list how much time that you spent on those. If you want to do that, that’s fine.</description></item></channel></rss>